iwantthatsound.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Notice — That Sound

### **THAT SOUND PRIVACY NOTICE**

This privacy policy describes the personal data collected or processed when you use www.iwantthatsound.com. This policy describes the types of personal data collected when you use our Site and how your personal data is used and protected. It also explains the choices you have relating to your personal data and how you can contact us.

 **WHO is Responsible for the Processing of Your Personal Data and WHAT is the legal basis for processing the data?**

THAT SOUND, LLC is responsible for processing your personal data and your consent is the lawful basis upon which we process your personal data.

 **WHAT Personal Data We Collect**

We ask you for certain personal data to provide you with our products. For example, when you make purchases, contact our consumer service, request to receive communications, create an account, participate in our events or contests, or interact with our Site.  This personal data includes your:  
Contact details including name, email, telephone number and shipping, billing address  
Login and account information, including screen name, password and unique user ID  
Personal details including gender, country, and purchase history (used to provide us with information about which of our products might interest you most)  
Payment or credit card information  
Images, photos and videos

 **WHY and HOW We Use Your Personal Data**

We use the personal data we collect from you in the following ways:

When you use our Site, we will use your data to provide the product you have selected.  For example, if you make a purchase on iwantthatsound.com, we will use the contact information you give us to communicate with you about the purchase. If you reach out to us via customer service, we will use information about you, such as delivery or payment information, or the product you have purchased to help us resolve your problem or question. Once you become an existing customer, we will use the email address you have provided to send you marketing communications related to THAT SOUND unless you chose to opt out of these communications. 

We may use the data you provide to us to operate our business.  For example, when you make a purchase, we may use that information for accounting, auditing and other internal functions.  As another example, we may use data about how you use our products to enhance your user experience and to help us diagnose technical and service problems and administer our site. 

We may also use data about how you use our sites to prevent, detect, or investigate fraud, abuse, illegal uses and violations of our Terms of Use and to comply with court orders, governmental request or applicable law.    
SHARING of Your Personal Data

We will not ever, for any reason, release any of your personal information to third parties. All information given to us by our customers is used exclusively by THAT SOUND, LLC.

###  **PROTECTION and MANAGEMENT of your Personal Data**

 **Encryption & Security: **We use a variety of technical, administrative, and organizational security measures, including encryption and authentication tools in certain circumstances, to maintain the safety of your personal data.   
Despite our efforts, no website, database or system is completely secure or “hacker proof.” You can help keep your data safe by taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse.   
Retention of your data: We retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which we collect it, except if required otherwise by law.

 **   
Managing your data:  **You may have the right to request: (i) access to your personal data; (ii) correction of your personal data if it is incomplete or inaccurate; or (iii) deletion of your personal data. You may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data on compelling legitimate grounds relating to your particular situation. Where we have obtained your consent for the processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data, including opting-out from the use for direct marketing purposes. If you have a request regarding your personal data that cannot be fulfilled from your account settings, please send a detailed request to support@iwantthatsound.com. **   **

###  **CHANGES to our Privacy Policy**

Applicable law and our practices change over time. If we decide to update our Policy, we will post the changes on our site. If we materially change the way in which we process personal data, we will provide you with prior notice, or where legally required, request your consent prior to implementing such changes. We strongly encourage you to read our Policy and keep yourself informed of our practices.

###  **QUESTIONS and Feedback**

We welcome questions, comments, and concerns about our Policy and privacy practices.  
If you wish to provide feedback or if you have questions or concerns, or wish to exercise your rights related to your personal data, please contact Customer Service at support@iwantthatsound.com.
